xhtmlchop.com 2016-10-29

# Xhtmlchop - Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy ("Privacy Statement") owned by XHTMLCHOP.com highlights the commitment and transparency in terms of the privacy maintained for its customers and visitors in interaction with XHTMLCHOP.com. The privacy section states that we may use the IP address of our site visitors to let us administer and help the various visitors to check the problems with the help of our web servers. To be able to provide appropriate information about the company, we need the personal and/ or contact information about the site users.

Note: XHTMLCHOP.com may have shared the links and content of numerous other websites here. XHTMLCHOP.com is not lawfully accountable for any such content as well privacy practice, applicable to their websites.

**GATHERING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION VOLUNTARILY**

Depending on the way you communicate with us, we collect your personal information including details such as your first name, last name, contact address, email address, date of birth, gender, phone number etc. This information is used with the consent of a user as it helps for better communication.

XHTMLCHOP.com ensures to keep a note on how your sensitive information is used and shared. Moreover, we give you an assurance that your confidential information is safe with us and not to be sold, disclosed, updated or shared with anybody under any situation other than our trustable resources & partners that provide assistance and support to your project.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH TECHNOLOGY**

On visiting our website, our web servers collect information such as your IP address/ domain names. This helps to evaluate statistics such as number of visits made on the website, pages viewed, amount of time spent on the site by a user etc. The main reason for evaluating the statistics is to take appropriate steps to boost the website services. This helps to improve the customer's experience and serve them far better than before. We gather information using cookies and navigational data (such as URL) to find the date & time of the visit, browser type, operating system etc.

**USE OF GATHERED INFORMATION**

The information that we collect or you submit, is useful to make our services better. This brings about an enhanced and personalized customer experience like providing quick response to the request against the queries, facilitating the quote, process transactions and so on. The gathered information will be shared with the third party in cases, if:

We feel it is essential to complete your ordered services.Providing better consultation according to your service request.We may use your personal information in providing promotional emails, RSS feed, electronic newsletters and latest offers related to your business interests. This is done only with your permission to "SUBSCRIBE". This can be unsubscribed as per the request at anytime.

**YOUR RIGHTS**

You have complete rights to stop receiving marketing emails, newsletter, RSS Feed and other sort of electronic communication through "unsubscribe" feature selected as per your rights.

**PRIVACY STATEMENT UPDATES**

Every time you use XHTMLCHOP.com, you are in consent with the practices and policies stated in the privacy statements. All the rights are reserved with XHTMLCHOP.com which makes the information offered for privacy practices to be amended, altered and/ or updated without preceding notice at any point of time. We recommend that you review the privacy statements regularly to properly understand our process for privacy. Using our site and its services regularly will show that you are in par with the modifications made to the policies and agree the terms and conditions cordially.

**INFORMATION SECURITY**

XHTMLCHOP.com ensures to stand by the high security benchmarks to protect your personal information from getting lost or misused. This gives an assurance that your personal information is away from every risk.

**CONTACT US**

If the information you provide is incomplete, incorrect or updated, please send us an email to get it updated soon with us. Also, if you find any query regarding our privacy statement, contact us via contact form or call: +1-888-825-8745.
